<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WSL on Koki&#39;s personal blog</title>
    <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/tags/wsl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in WSL on Koki&#39;s personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Powered by Hugo. Copyright © 2022 Koki NAKAMURA</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 14:37:55 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/tags/wsl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Install pyenv on WSL2 Ubuntu 22.04</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/python/installing-pyenv-pyenv-on-wsl-ubuntu2204/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 14:37:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/python/installing-pyenv-pyenv-on-wsl-ubuntu2204/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to install pyenv on Ubuntu 22.04 running on WSL2. From introducing the packages needed for pyenv&amp;rsquo;s installation to setting up pyenv itself, we cover the complete process. The following lists are the table of contents about this article. Target audience Environment Preconditions Contents 1. Installing Necessary Packages 2. Installing pyenv 3. Initial Configuration for pyenv Reference articles Target audience Those using WSL2 Individuals looking to manage Python versions efficiently Those aiming to install pyenv on Ubuntu Environment WSL2 Ubuntu 22.04 Preconditions Can access to the internet Contents 1. Installing Necessary Packages First, we need to install the packages required for pyenv. Execute the following command: sudo apt install -y gcc make build-essential libssl-dev libffi-dev zlib1g-dev libbz2-dev libreadline-dev libsqlite3-dev wget curl llvm libncurses5-dev xz-utils tk-dev libxml2-dev libxmlsec1-dev liblzma-dev 2. Installing pyenv Next,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to do when an error message is displayed when launching WSL2 Ubuntu and it cannot be started</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/other/resolve-wsl2-launch-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:55:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/other/resolve-wsl2-launch-error/</guid>
      <description>When you install Ubuntu for WSL2 via the Microsoft Store, there&amp;rsquo;s a chance you might face error messages upon launch. This article provides guidance on how to address these issues.
Table of Contents here.
 Target Audience Environment Prerequisites Issues with Microsoft Store Installation How to Resolve the Issue  1. Uninstalling Ubuntu on WSL2 2. Installing Ubuntu on WSL2 via Command Line Side Note: Checking Available Distributions    Target Audience  Those encountering error messages when starting WSL2 Ubuntu  Environment  Windows 10 or newer versions A setup where WSL2 can be utilized  Prerequisites  Activation of the Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL)  Issues with Microsoft Store Installation Upon installing Ubuntu for WSL2 via the Microsoft Store, you might see the following error messages, and Ubuntu on WSL2 might fail to start:
Command not found.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
