<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Koki&#39;s personal blog</title>
    <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Koki&#39;s personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 21:52:51 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding copy code button to Hugo blog</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/03/hugo-adding-copy-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 21:52:51 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/03/hugo-adding-copy-button/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to add a copy code button on Hugo blog.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Adding copy code button  Adding JavaScript code Adding CSS code  Reference articles   Target audience  Those who want to add a copy code button to code block on Hugo blog.   Environment  Hugo 0.57.2 Hugo-extended 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a title to code block on Hugo blog</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/02/hugo-code-block-title/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:30:24 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/02/hugo-code-block-title/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to add a title to code block on Hugo blog.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Add a title to code block  Add JavaScript code Add CSS code How to set a title  Reference articles   Target audience  Those who want to add a title to code block on Hugo blog.   Environment  Hugo 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a function of syntax highlight to Hugo blog</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/01/hugo-syntax-highlight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 20:50:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/01/hugo-syntax-highlight/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to add a function of syntax highlight on Hugo blog.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Add a function of syntax highlight Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to add a function of syntax highlight on Hugo blog.   Environment  Hugo 0.57.2 Hugo-extended 0.58.2   Preconditions  Installed Hugo and Hugo-extended   Add a function of syntax highlight Add the following codes to config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Ruby on Rails on Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/09/30/how-to-install-rails-on-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 18:55:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/09/30/how-to-install-rails-on-windows/</guid>
      <description>This article explain how to install Ruby on Rails on Windows 10.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Install How to check installed packages Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to create Ruby on Rails environment on Windows 10.   Environment  Windows 10 (1903) Chocolatey (0.10.15)   Preconditions  Already installed Chocolatey   Install Execute the following commands on Command Prompt or PowerShell as administrator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Chocolatey on Windows 10.</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/09/04/how-to-install-chocolatey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 16:38:27 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/09/04/how-to-install-chocolatey/</guid>
      <description>This article explain how to install Chocolatey on Windows 10.
Chocolatey is Package Management Tools that is like apt-get or yum on Linux.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience How to install Confirm Chocolatey is installed Install something to example How to check installed packages How to uninstall package How to update package Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to use functions like apt-get or yum on Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>