<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Koki&#39;s personal blog</title>
    <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Koki&#39;s personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Powered by Hugo. Copyright © 2022 Koki NAKAMURA</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:29:51 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignore auto-formatting a specific language on VS Code (Using Prettier)</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2022/02/25/ignore-auto-formatting-specific-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:29:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2022/02/25/ignore-auto-formatting-specific-language/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to gnore auto-formatting a specific language on VS Code (Using Prettier).
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Edit setting.json  1. Open setting.json 2. Disable specific language auto-formatting function   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to switch the on-off auto-formatting function on a specific language  Environment  Visual Studio Code  Preconditions  Install Prettier (Prettier is VS Code extention)  Edit setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up a Haskell development environment with VS Code on WSL2 (Ubuntu 20.04)</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2022/02/24/setup-haskell-dev-env-on-wsl2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 10:34:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2022/02/24/setup-haskell-dev-env-on-wsl2/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to set up a Haskell development environment with VS Code on WSL2 (Ubuntu 20.04).
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Set up the development environment  1. Install 2. Create a project 3. Prepare to enable build the project 4. Check setting up the development environment successful 5. Install VS Code extensions for development with Haskell   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to set up a Haskell development environment with VS Code on WSL2 (Ubuntu 20.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing pyenv, and Python by pyenv on WSL (Ubuntu 18.04 LTS)</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2020/04/26/installing-pyenv-pyenv-on-wsl-ubuntu1804/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 20:26:18 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2020/04/26/installing-pyenv-pyenv-on-wsl-ubuntu1804/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to install pyenv, and Python by pyenv on WSL (Ubuntu 18.04 LTS).
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Installing pyenv Installing Python by pyenv  Installing libraries that need for installing Python Installing Python   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to install pyenv and Python on WSL.  Environment  WSL (Ubuntu 18.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example codes about operating an embedded Vimeo video by JavaScript.</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/12/24/operating-vimeo-by-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:15:49 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/12/24/operating-vimeo-by-js/</guid>
      <description>This article explains the example codes of operating the embedded Vimeo video by JavaScript.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Operating an embedded Vimeo video by JavaScript  Loading the embedded Vimeo video to a HTML file Create a JavaScript file for each HTML file Create a JavaScript to operating the Vimeo video.   Example code Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to operating the Vimeo video by JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build an environment of Ruby on Rails tutorial on WSL</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/13/building-env-of-rails-tutorial-wsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 21:33:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/13/building-env-of-rails-tutorial-wsl/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to build the environment of Ruby on Rails tutorial on WSL.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Building the environment of Ruby on Rails tutorial Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to build the environment of Ruby on Rails tutorial on WSL.  Environment  Windows 10 (1903) Ubuntu (Distribution of WSL, have to use without version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying articles on Hugo blog automatically</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/08/deploying-articles-on-hugo-automatically/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 22:33:12 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/08/deploying-articles-on-hugo-automatically/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to deploy articles on Hugo blog automatically.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions How to deploy articles automatically  Make batch file Make PowerShell script file How to use script files    Target audience  Those who want to deploy articles automatically.  Environment  Windows 10 (1903) Command Prompt Power Shell (5.1.18362.145) Hugo (0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adjusting the display position of the &lt;a&gt; link destination in the same page (anchor)</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/07/adjusting-link-dests-position/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 18:31:02 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/07/adjusting-link-dests-position/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to adjust the display position of the &amp;lt;a&amp;gt; link destination in the same page.
If we are using a fixed header, we need to adjust the position of the anchor when clicked the &amp;lt;a&amp;gt; link.
Because the anchor is hidden behind the header.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Adjusting link destinations position Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to adjust the display position of the &amp;lt;a&amp;gt; link destination in the same page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a development environment of Node.js (Use Express and VS Code)</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/05/creating-dev-env-of-nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 21:09:21 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/05/creating-dev-env-of-nodejs/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to create a development environment of Node.js (Use Express) including a function of hot reload. (VS Code)
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Creating the development environment  Make project directory Install Express  Install Create a environment for test   Install Nodemon globally  Install Make a setting file Make and edit launch.json Edit package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a table of contents of Markdown automatically</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/04/making-table-of-contents-of-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 22:48:18 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/04/making-table-of-contents-of-markdown/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to make a table of contents of Markdown automatically..
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Preconditions Install doctoc Making a table of contents of Markdown automatically Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to make a table of contents of Markdown automatically.  Preconditions  Installed Node.js  Install doctoc Execute the following command.
npm install -g doctocMaking a table of contents of Markdown automatically Specify the directory where contains the Markdown file for making the table of contents exists in the doctoc parameter, and execute it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding copy code button to Hugo blog</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/03/hugo-adding-copy-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 21:52:51 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/03/hugo-adding-copy-button/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to add a copy code button on Hugo blog.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Adding copy code button  Adding JavaScript code Adding CSS code   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to add a copy code button to code block on Hugo blog.  Environment  Hugo 0.57.2 Hugo-extended 0.58.2  Preconditions  Installed Hugo and Hugo-extended  Adding copy code button Adding JavaScript code Add the following code to static/js/add-on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a title to code block on Hugo blog</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/02/hugo-code-block-title/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:30:24 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/02/hugo-code-block-title/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to add a title to code block on Hugo blog.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Add a title to code block  Add JavaScript code Add CSS code How to set a title   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to add a title to code block on Hugo blog.  Environment  Hugo 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a function of syntax highlight to Hugo blog</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/01/hugo-syntax-highlight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 20:50:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/10/01/hugo-syntax-highlight/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to add a function of syntax highlight on Hugo blog.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Add a function of syntax highlight Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to add a function of syntax highlight on Hugo blog.  Environment  Hugo 0.57.2 Hugo-extended 0.58.2  Preconditions  Installed Hugo and Hugo-extended  Add a function of syntax highlight Add the following codes to config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Ruby on Rails on Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/09/30/how-to-install-rails-on-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 18:55:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/09/30/how-to-install-rails-on-windows/</guid>
      <description>This article explain how to install Ruby on Rails on Windows 10.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Install How to check installed packages Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to create Ruby on Rails environment on Windows 10.  Environment  Windows 10 (1903) Chocolatey (0.10.15)  Preconditions  Already installed Chocolatey  Install Execute the following commands on Command Prompt or PowerShell as administrator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Chocolatey on Windows 10.</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/09/04/how-to-install-chocolatey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 16:38:27 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/2019/09/04/how-to-install-chocolatey/</guid>
      <description>This article explain how to install Chocolatey on Windows 10.
Chocolatey is Package Management Tools that is like apt-get or yum on Linux.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience How to install Confirm Chocolatey is installed Install something to example How to check installed packages How to uninstall package How to update package Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to use functions like apt-get or yum on Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>