<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Koki&#39;s personal blog</title>
    <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Koki&#39;s personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Powered by Hugo. Copyright © 2022 Koki NAKAMURA</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 14:37:55 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Install pyenv on WSL2 Ubuntu 22.04</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/python/installing-pyenv-pyenv-on-wsl-ubuntu2204/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 14:37:55 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/python/installing-pyenv-pyenv-on-wsl-ubuntu2204/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to install pyenv on Ubuntu 22.04 running on WSL2. From introducing the packages needed for pyenv&amp;rsquo;s installation to setting up pyenv itself, we cover the complete process. The following lists are the table of contents about this article. Target audience Environment Preconditions Contents 1. Installing Necessary Packages 2. Installing pyenv 3. Initial Configuration for pyenv Reference articles Target audience Those using WSL2 Individuals looking to manage Python versions efficiently Those aiming to install pyenv on Ubuntu Environment WSL2 Ubuntu 22.04 Preconditions Can access to the internet Contents 1. Installing Necessary Packages First, we need to install the packages required for pyenv. Execute the following command: sudo apt install -y gcc make build-essential libssl-dev libffi-dev zlib1g-dev libbz2-dev libreadline-dev libsqlite3-dev wget curl llvm libncurses5-dev xz-utils tk-dev libxml2-dev libxmlsec1-dev liblzma-dev 2. Installing pyenv Next,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to do when an error message is displayed when launching WSL2 Ubuntu and it cannot be started</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/other/resolve-wsl2-launch-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:55:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/other/resolve-wsl2-launch-error/</guid>
      <description>When you install Ubuntu for WSL2 via the Microsoft Store, there&amp;rsquo;s a chance you might face error messages upon launch. This article provides guidance on how to address these issues.
Table of Contents here.
 Target Audience Environment Prerequisites Issues with Microsoft Store Installation How to Resolve the Issue  1. Uninstalling Ubuntu on WSL2 2. Installing Ubuntu on WSL2 via Command Line Side Note: Checking Available Distributions    Target Audience  Those encountering error messages when starting WSL2 Ubuntu  Environment  Windows 10 or newer versions A setup where WSL2 can be utilized  Prerequisites  Activation of the Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL)  Issues with Microsoft Store Installation Upon installing Ubuntu for WSL2 via the Microsoft Store, you might see the following error messages, and Ubuntu on WSL2 might fail to start:
Command not found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Hugo article URLs structure as the same as under /content/ structure.</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/organizing-hugo-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 14:08:41 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/organizing-hugo-posts/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to setting Hugo article URLs structure as the same as under /content directory structure. The following lists are the table of contents about this article. Target audience Environment Preconditions Update Hugo Change setting to the config file. Example Reference articles Target audience Those who want to organize the posts by category, and setting URLs structure as the same as under /content directory structure. Environment WSL 2 (Ubuntu 20.04 LTS) Hugo Homebrew Preconditions Installed Hugo Installed Homebrew Update Hugo If your Hugo version is 0.83.0 or later, skip this section. If not, you need to upgrade Hugo because an attribute that is used in this article added at version 0.83.0. In this article case, uninstall Hugo by apt-get then re-install by Homebrew because apt-get repository has not known latest version Hugo. The re-install flow is the below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to do when an error message &#39;error: Failed to merge in the changes&#39; appears when executing brew update.</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/homebrew/homebrew-update-failed-to-merge-in-the-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 14:45:15 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/homebrew/homebrew-update-failed-to-merge-in-the-changes/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to solve an error message &amp;lsquo;error: Failed to merge in the changes&amp;rsquo; appears when executing brew update.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Executing brew update-reset What does brew update-reset command do? Reference articles  Target audience Those who want to break through the errors that occur when executing brew update and update Homebrew.
Environment  WSL 2 (Ubuntu 20.04 LTS)  Preconditions  Installed Homebrew  Executing brew update-reset Executing the below command to solve the problem.
brew update-reset That&amp;rsquo;s it!
What does brew update-reset command do? Homebrew official and non-official remote repository information are reset, then reacquired and reconfigured.
Reference articles Homebrew Documentation: update-reset 
install brew error error: Failed to merge in the changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add a robots.txt to the site Hugo builds.</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/add-robots-txt-to-hugo-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 15:17:30 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/add-robots-txt-to-hugo-site/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to add robots.txt to the site Hugo builds.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Add setting to the config file Create the robots.txt under the layouts directory Example Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to add a robots.txt to the site Hugo builds.  Environment  Hugo (v0.94.2+extended linux/amd64 BuildDate=unknown)  Preconditions  Installed Hugo.  Add setting to the config file Add the below code to top-level in the config file.
In this site case, I added the below code because the config file type is toml.
enableRobotsTXT = true If you use a YAML type config file, add the below code.
enableRobotsTXT: true If you use a JSON type config file, add the below code.
&amp;#34;enableRobotsTXT&amp;#34;: true Hugo will create the robots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About installing Jest, and how to set up intellisense and how solving an import error.</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/javascript/install-and-setting-jest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 22:24:57 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/javascript/install-and-setting-jest/</guid>
      <description>[17/03/2022] Fix the npm install command in the set up intellisense section.
This article explains how to install Jest, how to set up intellisense and how solving an import error.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Install Jest Set up intellisense Set up for solving an import error Digression  Why did I choose Jest for JavaScript testing? Why do I use both npm and yarn?   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to build Jest environment.  Environment  Windows 10 (Ver. 21H2, Build. 19044.1526) WSL 2 (Ubuntu 20.04 LTS) Visual Studio Code  Preconditions  Installed npm and yarn  Install Jest npm install --save-dev jest Set up intellisense Firstly, execute the below command to install Jest type definitions.
npm install --save-dev @types/jest Then create a jsconfig.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignore auto-formatting a specific language on VS Code (Using Prettier)</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/visual-studio-code/ignore-auto-formatting-specific-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 16:29:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/visual-studio-code/ignore-auto-formatting-specific-language/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to gnore auto-formatting a specific language on VS Code (Using Prettier).
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Edit setting.json  1. Open setting.json 2. Disable specific language auto-formatting function   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to switch the on-off auto-formatting function on a specific language  Environment  Visual Studio Code  Preconditions  Install Prettier (Prettier is VS Code extention)  Edit setting.json 1. Open setting.json Pushing Ctrl + Shift + P simultaneously then choosing Preferences: Open Settings(JSON).
If your environment is Mac OS, push Command + Shift + P instead of Ctrl + Shift + P.
2. Disable specific language auto-formatting function Add the below line to a specific language section.
&amp;#34;editor.formatOnSave&amp;#34;: false e.g. Add to markdown section.
&amp;#34;[markdown]&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up a Haskell development environment with VS Code on WSL2 (Ubuntu 20.04)</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/haskell/setup-haskell-dev-env-on-wsl2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 10:34:12 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/haskell/setup-haskell-dev-env-on-wsl2/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to set up a Haskell development environment with VS Code on WSL2 (Ubuntu 20.04).
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Set up the development environment  1. Install 2. Create a project 3. Prepare to enable build the project 4. Check setting up the development environment successful 5. Install VS Code extensions for development with Haskell   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to set up a Haskell development environment with VS Code on WSL2 (Ubuntu 20.04).  Environment  Windows 10 (Ver. 21H2, Build. 19044.1526) WSL 2 (Ubuntu 20.04 LTS)  Preconditions  Install WSL 2 (Ubuntu 20.04 LTS) to Windows 10 Install VS Code to WSL 2  Set up the development environment 1. Install wget -qO- https://get.haskellstack.org/ | sh 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing pyenv, and Python by pyenv on WSL (Ubuntu 18.04 LTS)</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/python/installing-pyenv-pyenv-on-wsl-ubuntu1804/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 20:26:18 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/python/installing-pyenv-pyenv-on-wsl-ubuntu1804/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to install pyenv, and Python by pyenv on WSL (Ubuntu 18.04 LTS).
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Installing pyenv Installing Python by pyenv  Installing libraries that need for installing Python Installing Python   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to install pyenv and Python on WSL.  Environment  WSL (Ubuntu 18.04 LTS)  Preconditions  Already installed git.  Installing pyenv Execution the following commands.
git clone https://github.com/pyenv/pyenv.git ~/.pyenv echo &amp;#39;export PYENV_ROOT=&amp;#34;$HOME/.pyenv&amp;#34;&amp;#39; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; ~/.bash_profile echo &amp;#39;export PATH=&amp;#34;$PYENV_ROOT/bin:$PATH&amp;#34;&amp;#39; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; ~/.bash_profile echo -e &amp;#39;if command -v pyenv 1&amp;gt;/dev/null 2&amp;gt;&amp;amp;1; then\n eval &amp;#34;$(pyenv init -)&amp;#34;\nfi&amp;#39; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; ~/.bash_profile exec &amp;#34;$SHELL&amp;#34; Then reboot WSL for applying the setting.
Installation of pyenv is now complete.
Installing Python by pyenv Installing libraries that need for installing Python Execution the following command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example codes about operating an embedded Vimeo video by JavaScript.</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/javascript/operating-vimeo-by-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:15:49 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/javascript/operating-vimeo-by-js/</guid>
      <description>This article explains the example codes of operating the embedded Vimeo video by JavaScript.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Operating an embedded Vimeo video by JavaScript  Loading the embedded Vimeo video to a HTML file Create a JavaScript file for each HTML file Create a JavaScript to operating the Vimeo video.   Example code Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to operating the Vimeo video by JavaScript.  Environment  JavaScript (ES2015)  Preconditions Nothing.
Operating an embedded Vimeo video by JavaScript Loading the embedded Vimeo video to a HTML file First, load the embedded Vimeo video to a HTML file by iframe.
In this article case, using a sample Vimeo video.
&amp;lt;html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;script type=&amp;#34;module&amp;#34; src=&amp;#34;./javascript/index.js&amp;#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!-- Specific your video URL on src attribute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build an environment of Ruby on Rails tutorial on WSL</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/ruby-on-rails/building-env-of-rails-tutorial-wsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 21:33:28 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/ruby-on-rails/building-env-of-rails-tutorial-wsl/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to build the environment of Ruby on Rails tutorial on WSL. The following lists are the table of contents about this article. Target audience Environment Preconditions Building the environment of Ruby on Rails tutorial Reference articles Target audience Those who want to build the environment of Ruby on Rails tutorial on WSL. Environment Windows 10 (1903) Ubuntu (Distribution of WSL, have to use without version.) Preconditions Enable the function of WSL Installed Ubuntu (WSL) Building the environment of Ruby on Rails tutorial Execute the following commands. That&amp;rsquo;s it! # Install necessary tools sudo apt update sudo apt upgrade -y sudo apt install autoconf bison build-essential libssl1.0-dev libyaml-dev libreadline-dev zlib1g-dev libncurses5-dev libffi-dev libgdbm-dev sqlite3 libsqlite3-dev nodejs-dev node-gyp npm git -y sudo npm install --global yarn # Install rbenv git clone https://github.com/rbenv/rbenv.git ~/.rbenv echo &amp;#39;export PATH=&amp;#34;$HOME/.rbenv/bin:$PATH&amp;#34;&amp;#39; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; ~/.bashrc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying articles on Hugo blog automatically</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/deploying-articles-on-hugo-automatically/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 22:33:12 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/deploying-articles-on-hugo-automatically/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to deploy articles on Hugo blog automatically.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions How to deploy articles automatically  Make batch file Make PowerShell script file How to use script files    Target audience  Those who want to deploy articles automatically.  Environment  Windows 10 (1903) Command Prompt Power Shell (5.1.18362.145) Hugo (0.57.2) Hugo-extended (0.58.2)  Preconditions  Manage blog posts on GitHub. Cloned Hugo blog repository as &amp;ldquo;public&amp;rdquo; directory.  How to deploy articles automatically Make script files, then execute it.
In this case, use batch file and Powershell script file because use batch file is easier to execute PowerShell script file.
Make batch file Make &amp;ldquo;deploy.bat&amp;rdquo; file in blog root directory and copy and paste the following codes to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adjusting the display position of the &lt;a&gt; link destination in the same page (anchor)</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/css/adjusting-link-dests-position/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 18:31:02 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/css/adjusting-link-dests-position/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to adjust the display position of the &amp;lt;a&amp;gt; link destination in the same page. If we are using a fixed header, we need to adjust the position of the anchor when clicked the &amp;lt;a&amp;gt; link. Because the anchor is hidden behind the header. The following lists are the table of contents about this article. Target audience Environment Preconditions Adjusting link destinations position Reference articles Target audience Those who want to adjust the display position of the &amp;lt;a&amp;gt; link destination in the same page. Environment CSS3 Preconditions Nothing. Adjusting link destinations position Setting the following codes to the target anchor tag to add-on.css. When you set it, you must set the same number to padding-top and margin-top. #target-tag { display: block; padding-top: 60px; margin-top: -60px; } In this blog, I adjust the headings in the post using</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a development environment of Node.js (Use Express and VS Code)</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/nodejs/creating-dev-env-of-nodejs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 21:09:21 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/nodejs/creating-dev-env-of-nodejs/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to create a development environment of Node.js (Use Express) including a function of hot reload. (VS Code)
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Creating the development environment  Make project directory Install Express  Install Create a environment for test   Install Nodemon globally  Install Make a setting file Make and edit launch.json Edit package.json   How to execute in debug mode   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to create the development environment of Node.js (Express) on VS Code.  Environment  Windows 10 (1903) Visual Studio Code (1.38.1) Node.js (v10.16.3) npm (6.11.2)  Preconditions  Installed Node.js, npm and VS Code  Creating the development environment Make project directory Execute the following command to make the directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a table of contents of Markdown automatically</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/markdown/making-table-of-contents-of-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 22:48:18 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/markdown/making-table-of-contents-of-markdown/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to make a table of contents of Markdown automatically..
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Preconditions Install doctoc Making a table of contents of Markdown automatically Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to make a table of contents of Markdown automatically.  Preconditions  Installed Node.js  Install doctoc Execute the following command.
npm install -g doctoc Making a table of contents of Markdown automatically Specify the directory where contains the Markdown file for making the table of contents exists in the doctoc parameter, and execute it. For the following example, specifying current directory.
doctoc . Wait to show &amp;ldquo;Everything is OK.&amp;rdquo;. Then open the file, the table of contents has been added to the top between the following comments.
&amp;lt;!-- START doctoc generated TOC please keep comment here to allow auto update --&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding copy code button to Hugo blog</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/hugo-adding-copy-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 21:52:51 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/hugo-adding-copy-button/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to add a copy code button on Hugo blog.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Adding copy code button  Adding JavaScript code Adding CSS code   Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to add a copy code button to code block on Hugo blog.  Environment  Hugo 0.57.2 Hugo-extended 0.58.2  Preconditions  Installed Hugo and Hugo-extended  Adding copy code button Adding JavaScript code Add the following code to static/js/add-on.js.
I use IIFE (Immediately Invoked Function Expression) because I want to narrow the scope of a variable.
(() =&amp;gt; { &amp;#39;use strict&amp;#39;; if(!document.queryCommandSupported(&amp;#39;copy&amp;#39;)) { return; } function flashCopyMessage(el, msg) { el.textContent = msg; setTimeout(() =&amp;gt; { el.textContent = &amp;#34;Copy&amp;#34;; }, 1000); } function selectText(node) { let selection = window.getSelection(); let range = document.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a title to code block on Hugo blog</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/hugo-code-block-title/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 21:30:24 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/hugo-code-block-title/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to add a title to code block on Hugo blog. The following lists are the table of contents about this article. Target audience Environment Preconditions Add a title to code block Add JavaScript code Add CSS code How to set a title Reference articles Target audience Those who want to add a title to code block on Hugo blog. Environment Hugo 0.57.2 Hugo-extended 0.58.2 Preconditions Installed Hugo and Hugo-extended Add a title to code block Add JavaScript code Add the following code to static/js/add-on.js. I use IIFE (Immediately Invoked Function Expression) because I want to narrow the scope of a variable. (function addTitleToCodeBlock() { let list = document.body.getElementsByClassName(&amp;#34;highlight&amp;#34;); for (i = 0; i &amp;lt;= list.length - 1; i++) { let code = list[i].firstElementChild.firstElementChild; let codeName = code ? code.className.split(&amp;#34;:&amp;#34;)[1] : null; if (codeName) { let div</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a function of syntax highlight to Hugo blog</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/hugo-syntax-highlight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 20:50:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/hugo/hugo-syntax-highlight/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how to add a function of syntax highlight on Hugo blog.
The following lists are the table of contents about this article.
 Target audience Environment Preconditions Add a function of syntax highlight Reference articles  Target audience  Those who want to add a function of syntax highlight on Hugo blog.  Environment  Hugo 0.57.2 Hugo-extended 0.58.2  Preconditions  Installed Hugo and Hugo-extended  Add a function of syntax highlight Add the following codes to config.toml.
pygmentsCodefences = true pygmentsStyle = &amp;#34;fruity&amp;#34; You can chose a style on pygmentsStyle from the below pages.
Chroma Style GalleryxxxxxxxxxxThe above code chooses style that is &amp;ldquo;fruity&amp;rdquo;.
Reference articles Syntax highlighting in Hugo with Chroma | zwbetzxxxxxxxxxx</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Ruby on Rails on Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/ruby-on-rails/how-to-install-rails-on-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 18:55:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/ruby-on-rails/how-to-install-rails-on-windows/</guid>
      <description>This article explain how to install Ruby on Rails on Windows 10. The following lists are the table of contents about this article. Target audience Environment Preconditions Install How to check installed packages Reference articles Target audience Those who want to create Ruby on Rails environment on Windows 10. Environment Windows 10 (1903) Chocolatey (0.10.15) Preconditions Already installed Chocolatey Install Execute the following commands on Command Prompt or PowerShell as administrator. REM Install Yarn choco install yarn -y REM Install Ruby choco install ruby -y REM Install msys2 choco install msys2 --params &amp;#34;/NoUpdate&amp;#34; -y refreshenv ridk install 2 3 REM Install SQLite gem uninstall sqlite3 --all ridk exec pacman -S mingw-w64-x86_64-sqlite3 gem install sqlite3 --platform ruby REM Install bundle gem install bundle REM Install Ruby on Rails gem install rails If you want to specify version Ruby and Ruby on</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Chocolatey on Windows 10.</title>
      <link>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/chocolatey/how-to-install-chocolatey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 16:38:27 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://koki-nakamura22.github.io/blog/posts/chocolatey/how-to-install-chocolatey/</guid>
      <description>This article explain how to install Chocolatey on Windows 10. Chocolatey is Package Management Tools that is like apt-get or yum on Linux. The following lists are the table of contents about this article. Target audience How to install Confirm Chocolatey is installed Install something to example How to check installed packages How to uninstall package How to update package Reference articles Target audience Those who want to use functions like apt-get or yum on Windows. How to install Execute the following command on Command Prompt as Administrator. @&amp;#34;%SystemRoot%\System32\WindowsPowerShell\v1.0\powershell.exe&amp;#34; -NoProfile -InputFormat None -ExecutionPolicy Bypass -Command &amp;#34;iex ((New-Object System.Net.WebClient).DownloadString(&amp;#39;https://chocolatey.org/install.ps1&amp;#39;))&amp;#34; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; SET &amp;#34;PATH=%PATH%;%ALLUSERSPROFILE%\chocolatey\bin&amp;#34; Or, execute the following command on PowerShell as Administrator. Set-ExecutionPolicy Bypass -Scope Process -Force; iex ((New-Object System.Net.WebClient).DownloadString(&amp;#39;https://chocolatey.org/install.ps1&amp;#39;)) Confirm Chocolatey is installed After execute install, execute the following command on Command Prompt or PowerShell. choco -v If version information appears</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
